

## SHAUN SEIDMAN

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

### CONTACT



shaunseidman@gmail.com



(949)599-4271



shaunseidman.com



1600 Glenarm Pl #806, Denver, CO 80202

### **ABOUT**

Thanks for taking a look. I am a full stack developer with a passion for creating, problem solving and continuing to learn and grow. My previous experience in managing a small business and team building have helped to solidify my work techniques with others and also instill a never-quit attitude.

### **SKILLS**

Knex

Python

Express

Node.Js

Postgresql

- Javascript
- CSS
- HTML
- Vue.Js
- Swift
- Git
- Agile
- Cypress
- SASS

### **PROJECTS**

#### shaunseidman.com

A work in progress personal website made with Vue.JS

#### http://cute-middle.surge.sh/#/

.A full stack web CRUD app using Vue.JS, Knex, postgresql, bootstrap and Chart.JS. A fun and easy way to compare retail vs resell sneaker prices by uploading them to a database.

### Fridge Vision

A collaborative group project implementing React Native, Clarafi image recognition and Amazon Web Services S3 image hosting.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Proper Barbershop - General Manager - March 2016 - November 2017

As the GM I created accounts with wholesale men's grooming products to carry in store. As well as managing inventory and the 15 barbers, I was in charge of accounts payable and helped open a second location.

# Novo Coffee - Store Manager - February 2015 - March 2016 Manage the cafe as well as place order and make the weekly schedule for 7 employees

### Native Foods - Assistant Store Manager November 2014 - February 2015

Created schedule for both front and back of house employees. Assisted and served customers as well worked back of house shifts when need be

# ZMediaNow LLC- Customer Service Manager February 2013 - October 2014

Managed a team of 10 customer service representatives

### **EDUCATION**

### Galvanize Web Development Immersive

November 2017 - May 2018

#### **Orange Coast College**

June 2009 - December 2011

#### Sonoma State University

August 2008 - June 2009